Guide to the John McComb Architectural Drawings Finding Aid 1766-1829 PR 40
New-York Historical Society
- Church steeple, unidentified, 93114 (Box McComb box 4, Item 66)
- Church, pulpit, unidentifed, 93113 (Box McComb box 4, Item 60)
- Church, unidentified, 93112 (Box McComb Box 15, Item 262)
- Church, unidentified, 93111 (Box McComb box 3, Item 48)
- Church, unidentified, 93110 (Box McComb Box 15, Item 264)
- Church, unidentified, 93109 (Box McComb Box 10, Item 179)
- Church, unidentified, 93108 (Box McComb Box 19, Item 393)
- Church, unidentified, 93107 (Box McComb Box 8, Item 131)
- Church, unidentified, 93106 (Box McComb box 4, Item 63)
- Church, unidentified ink, UC: "Side View", 93105 (Box McComb Box 14, Item 229)
- Church, unidentified, 93104 (Box McComb Box 14, Item 231)
- Church, unidentified, "Mch 15/05": pencil, LR; 93103 (Box McComb Box 14, Item 230)
- Church, unidentified, 93102 (Box McComb box 4, Item 071a recto)
- Church, unidentified graphite, LL: "Pulpit", 93101 (Box McComb Box 9, Item 143)
- Church, unidentified Two sections looking toward pulpit [attrib.], 93100 (Box McComb Box 9, Item 141)
- Church, unidentified Two sections looking toward pulpit, 93099 (Box McComb Box 9, Item 142)
- Church, unidentified, 93098 (Box McComb box 2, Item 41)
- Church, unidentified List of dimensions: attributed, 93097 (Box McComb Box 15, Item 261)
- Church, unidentified, 93096 (Box McComb Box 8, Item 132)
- Church, unidentified, 93095 (Box McComb box 3, Item 49)
- [Church, unidentified], 93204 (Box McComb Box 13, Item 222)
- Church, unidentified [Gothic], 93094 (Box McComb Box 10, Item 172)
- Church, unidentified [Gothic] ink, UL-UC: "St. Marys Church Lincoln"; ink, LC: "York Cath.l", 93093 (Box McComb Box 10, Item 173)
- Church, unidentified [Gothic], 93092 (Box McComb Box 10, Item 178)
- Church, unidentified [Gothic] ink, UR-UC:"Rough Calculation for Piers at N. River", 93091 (Box McComb Box 10, Item 174 recto)
- Church, unidentified [Gothic], 93090 (Box McComb Box 10, Item 171)
- Church, unidentified [Gothic], 93089 (Box McComb Box 10, Item 170)
- Church, unidentified [Gothic] [Wall St. Presbyterian], 1823; April 3; 93088 (Box McComb Box 10, Item 177)
- Church, unidentified [Gothic] central plan, 93087 (Box McComb Box 10, Item 175)
- Church, unidentified [Gothic], [Wall St. Presbyterian?], 1823; March 31; 93086 (Box McComb Box 10, Item 176)
- Church, unidentified. Brick Presbyterian Church alteration [attrib], [1822 - 1823]; 93085 (Box McComb box 2, Item 040a)
- Church, unidentified. Brick Presbyterian Church alteration [attrib], [1822 - 1823]; 93084 (Box McComb box 2, Item 042b)
- Church, unidentified. Brick Presbyterian Church alteration, attrib., [1822 - 1823]; 93083 (Box McComb box 2, Item 042a)
- Church, unidentified. Brick Presbytrian Church alteration [attrib], [1822 - 1823].; 93082 (Box McComb box 2, Item 040b)
- Church, unidentified. North Dutch [attrib], 93081 (Box McComb box 3, Item 45)
- Church, unidentified. North Dutch [attrib], 93080 (Box McComb box 3, Item 46)
- Church, unidentified; circular plan [aka central plan auditorium and arena plan.], [1811]; 93079 (Box McComb box 3, Item 44)
- Circular building elevation, attributed A domed building with Pediment and columns (Cf. Pantheon): attributed, 93078 (Box McComb Box 17, Item 340)
- Circular building plan, 93077 (Box McComb Box 9, Item 150)
- Circular building plan, attributed Plan of a circular church with columed porticoes on four sides: attributed, 93076 (Box McComb Box 17, Item 341)
- City Hall City Hall: attributed, [1802-1811]; 93075 (Box McComb Box 12, Item 200)
- City Hall Grand stairway: attrib., 1803; 93074 (Box Drawer 24, Item CH066)
- City Hall Grand Stairway: attrib., 1803; 93073 (Box Drawer 23, Item CH065)
- City Hall Front Elevation: attrib., 1802; 93072 (Box Drawer 15, Item CH001)
- City Hall Urns in niches sketch: attrib., 1803; 93071 (Box Drawer 23, Item CH065 verso)
- City Hall Plan: attrib., 1803; 93070 (Box Drawer 24, Item CH066 verso)
- City Hall Wall section: attrib., 1804; 93069 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH050 1/2)
- City Hall "as Executed": ink, LC Roof Trusses: attrib., 1804; 93068 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH050)
- City Hall Volutes, 1803; 93067 (Box Drawer 25, Item CH097A verso)
- City Hall "Console for 2"d Order at Full Size": ink, LC, 1803; 93066 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH085 1/2)
- City Hall "First idea for the Cupola of City Hall}": ink, ML, 1803; 93065 (Box Drawer 22, Item CH055 1/2)
- City Hall "Sketch of Finish round udges Seat in Mayors Court Room": pencil, LC, 1810; 93064 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH074)
- City Hall "Entablature in Common Council Chamber": pencil, LC, 1803; 93063 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH072)
- City Hall "Judges Table": pencil, LC, 1803; 93062 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH073)
- City Hall Sketches for soffit of dome, 1804; 93061 (Box Drawer 24, Item CH069 1/2)
- City Hall "Moulding for Tablet on South Front 1/2 Size": ink, LR or Partial Elevation - South Front: attrib., 1803; 93060 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH045)
- City Hall "Cornice at the foot of the Cove": ink, LL-LC, 1803; 93059 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH071)
- City Hall "Elevation of One half the Gallery Stretched out": pencil, MC, 1803; 93058 (Box Drawer 23, Item CH063)
- City Hall "This by ESW used by him on his residence": pencil, LC-LR, 1803; 93057 (Box Drawer 23, Item CH061 verso)
- City Hall Roof Structure: attrib., 1803; 93056 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH423)
- City Hall "Jno Moore No 14 Rose St.-": ink, UR, 1803; 93055 (Box Drawer 24, Item CH088 verso)
- City Hall "Entablature for Mayors Court Room": ink, UR-MR, 1803; 93054 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH084)
- City Hall "Entablature in Large Court Room 2'-6"-": ink, MC, 1803; 93053 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH085)
- City Hall "whole width of Soffit between Col. of Portico": pencil, MC, 1803; 93052 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH062 verso)
- City Hall A door with transom: attrib., 1803; 93051 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH082 1/2)
- City Hall Court Room: attrib., 1803; 93050 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH077)
- City Hall Section from Rotunda to Exterior: attrib., 1803; 93049 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH083)
- City Hall Capital - interior vestibule: attrib., 1803; 93048 (Box Drawer 23, Item CH061)
- City Hall "2"d Order of New City Hall": partial title, ink, ML, [1803]; 93047 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH041)
- City Hall Designs for Iron Railings: attrib., 1803; 93046 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH094)
- City Hall Marble Flooring - scale given, 1805; 93045 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH070)
- City Hall Circular corridor plan: attrib., 1803; 93044 (Box Drawer 23, Item CH064 1/2)
- City Hall Sketches: attrib., 1803; 93043 (Box Drawer 22, Item CH055 3/4 verso)
- City Hall Interior Vestibule: attrib., 1803; 93042 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH062)
- City Hall Lesser Stairway Section: attrib., 1803; 93041 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH081)
- City Hall Grand Stairway: attrib., 1803; 93040 (Box Drawer 23, Item CH064)
- City Hall "Section of Common Council Chambers": pencil, UL-UC, 1804; 93039 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH080)
- City Hall Grand Stair: attrib., 1803; 93038 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH105)
- City Hall Court Room with Judge's Canopy: attrib., 1803; 93037 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH079)
- City Hall "For the Arms of the United States. For the Arms of the State of New York.": ink, LL-LR, 1803; 93036 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH095)
- City Hall Grand Stair Detail and Column Detail: attrib., 1803; 93035 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH105 verso)
- City Hall Designs for Iron Railings: attrib., 1803; 93034 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH093)
- City Hall Court Room: attrib., 1803; 93033 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH075)
- City Hall "Cornices only of City Hall": ink, UL, 1803; 93032 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH084 verso)
- City Hall Section through Grand Stairway, Gallery Dome and Cupola: attrib., 1803; 93031 (Box Drawer 24, Item CH067)
- City Hall Showing entrance of floor beams and sleepers: attrib., 1803; 93030 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH082)
- City Hall "Plan of Attic Story": pencil, MC, 1803; 93029 (Box Drawer 20, Item CH049)
- City Hall "Entablature for Inside of Colonnade":, 1803; 93028 (Box Drawer 18, Item CH025 1/2)
- City Hall "Elevation of One half the North. Front. Basement.": ink, LC-LR, 1804; 93027 (Box Drawer 16, Item CH010)
- City Hall "Capitals for 2.d Order of Pilasters for New City Hall": ink, ML, 1804; 93026 (Box Drawer 19, Item CH043)
- City Hall "Ionic Base at Large": ink, LC, 1803; 93025 (Box Drawer 9, Item CH019 1/2)
- City Hall "section Lenghtways of a part of Colonnade": ink, ML-MC, 1803; 93024 (Box Drawer 18, Item CH024)
- City Hall Plan and Entablature of Colonnade: attrib., 1803; 93023 (Box Drawer 18, Item CH025)
- City Hall Partial Plan: attrib., 1803; 93022 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH381 verso)
- City Hall Elevation [vestibule]: attrib., 1803; 93021 (Box Drawer 10, Item CH030 verso)
- City Hall Plan of Second Floor: attrib., 1804; 93020 (Box Drawer 8, Item CH015)
- City Hall Roof Plan: attrib., 1803; 93019 (Box Drawer 17, Item CH018)
- City Hall Partial Front Elevation with Clock: attrib., 1803; 93018 (Box Drawer 20, Item CH046)
- City Hall Main Floor Plan: attrib., 1803; 93017 (Box Drawer 17, Item CH013)
- City Hall Ionic base, column, capital, entablature of First Order: attrib., 1803; 93016 (Box Drawer 9, Item CH019)
- City Hall North-South Section through Center of City Hall: attrib., 1802; 93015 (Box Drawer 15, Item CH003)
- City Hall Elevation Base of Cupola: attrib., 1803; 93014 (Box Drawer 22, Item CH056)
- City Hall "Base for Vestibule": ink, LR, 1803; 93013 (Box Drawer 10, Item CH028 1/2)
- City Hall "SENECA Il Filosofo": ink, LC, 1803; 93012 (Box Drawer 25, Item CH096)
- City Hall "over Grand Stairs City Hall": pencil, MC-LC, 1803; 93011 (Box Drawer 22, Item CH053 1/2)
- City Hall Rear Elevation, 1802; 93010 (Box Drawer 15, Item CH002)
- City Hall Column or entablature detail: attrib., 1803; 93009 (Box Drawer 10, Item CH029 verso)
- City Hall "the Tower will be Seen from the Park as it is drawn": ink, UC, 1803; 93008 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH386)
- City Hall Design of the Cupola as executed: attrib., 1803; 93007 (Box Drawer 22, Item CH056 1/2 verso)
- City Hall Designs for statuary, shown on drawings but not executed, 1803; 93006 (Box Drawer 25, Item CH098)
- City Hall "West Projection of South Front": ink, LL-LR, 1803; 93005 (Box Drawer 16, Item CH007)
- City Hall Designs for Statuary shown on drawings but not executed, 1803; 93004 (Box Drawer 25, Item CH097A)
- City Hall Urn: attrib., 1803; 93003 (Box Drawer 21, Item CH054)
- City Hall "Ornaments executed on the chimney pieces in the Common Council Chamber City Hall-": ink, UL-UR, 1803; 93002 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH080 1/2)
- City Hall "Park - contains upwards of 4 acres-": ink, MC, 1803; 93001 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH089)
- City Hall Same. Another view. Justice - rear view., 1803; 93000 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH059)
- City Hall Design, statuary for Cupola base, south front: attrib., 1805; 92999 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH051)
- City Hall Figure Surmounting Cupola, as executed., 1803; 92998 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH058)
- City Hall "Plan of the First Floor": pencil, LC, 1804; 92997 (Box Drawer 17, Item CH014)
- City Hall Cupola: attrib., 1803; 92996 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH391)
- City Hall "Balusters for New City Hall": ink, ML-MR, 1803; 92995 (Box Drawer 11, Item CH038)
- City Hall Interior elevations: attrib., 1803; 92994 (Box Drawer 22, Item CH056 verso)
- City Hall "Entrance to the principal Stairs": ink, UL, 1803; 92993 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH068)
- City Hall Base of Cupola: attrib., 1803; 92992 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH048 1/2)
- City Hall Working drawing of console used by stone cutters: attrib., 1803; 92991 (Box Drawer 11, Item CH032)
- City Hall Attic front w/moulding for panels: attrib., 1803; 92990 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH047)
- City Hall "Entablature of 2.d Order at Half Size-": ink, MR, 1803; 92989 (Box Drawer 18, Item CH035)
- City Hall Windows elevation: attrib., 1803; 92988 (Box Drawer 10, Item CH027)
- City Hall "Architrave of 2"d Order at full Size-": ink, LL, 1803; 92987 (Box Drawer 11, Item CH036 1/2)
- City Hall Sketch - Attic Front: attrib., 1803; 92986 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH048)
- City Hall Another Cornice, 1803; 92985 (Box Drawer 24, Item CH087 1/2)
- City Hall Window and Door transoms: attrib., 1803; 92984 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH079 1/2)
- City Hall "Baluster for Pedestal of 2"d Order at full Size" w/ seraph: ink, MC-MR, 1803; 92983 (Box Drawer 11, Item CH039 1/2)
- City Hall Sketch of detail: attrib. [Console/bracket], 1803; 92982 (Box Drawer 21, Item CH052 verso)
- City Hall Elevation: attrib., 1803; 92981 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH388)
- City Hall "Plan of the Cupola for New City Hall": ink, LL-LR, 1803; 92980 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH055)
- City Hall "Cornice for 2"d Order": ink, LC-LR, 1803; 92979 (Box Drawer 11, Item CH036)
- City Hall "17 3/4"- for Columns, at Top": pencil, LC, 1803; 92978 (Box Drawer 9, Item CH021)
- City Hall "Basement Story": ink, LC, 1803; 92977 (Box Drawer 8, Item CH012)
- City Hall Colonnade balustrade: attrib., 1803; 92976 (Box Drawer 10, Item CH026)
- City Hall "Console for Vestibule": ink, LC, 1803; 92975 (Box Drawer 10, Item CH028)
- City Hall "Console at half Size": ink, LR, 1803; 92974 (Box Drawer 10, Item CH030)
- City Hall Some of floor timbering of second floor: attrib., 1803; 92973 (Box Drawer 9, Item CH017)
- City Hall "Dentils were left out in Execution. " " added in 1"st order - Ionic E.S. Wilde,": pencil, UL, [1803]; 92972 (Box Drawer 11, Item CH034)
- City Hall Urns: attrib., 1803; 92971 (Box Drawer 21, Item CH054 verso)
- City Hall "Capital for Vestibule City Hall-": ink, LR, 1803; 92970 (Box Drawer 9, Item CH020)
- City Hall Details: attrib., 1804; 92969 (Box Drawer 20, Item CH046 1/2)
- City Hall Entablature First Order: attrib., 1803; 92968 (Box Drawer 9, Item CH022)
- City Hall "Cornice of the first order at full size": ink, MC-MR, 1803; 92967 (Box Drawer 9, Item CH022 1/2)
- City Hall "Archivolt of the first order For New City Hall": ink, MC, 1803; 92966 (Box Drawer 9, Item CH023 1/2)
- City Hall "Impost of the first order for New City Hall": ink, UC-UR, 1803; 92965 (Box Drawer 9, Item CH023)
- City Hall Sketch - Elevation of Cupola: attrib., 1803; 92964 (Box Drawer 22, Item CH055 3/4)
- City Hall "Base and Cap for Pedestal at full Size for the 2d Order-": ink, ML-MC, 1803; 92963 (Box Drawer 11, Item CH039)
- City Hall "Rear Front": ink, MR, 1803; 92962 (Box Drawer 18, Item CH031)
- City Hall Entablature details: attrib., 1803; 92961 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH106)
- City Hall "Half the Center Arch of South Front 3'-3 1/2"-": ink, LC, 1803; 92960 (Box Drawer 10, Item CH029)
- City Hall Section Grand Stair and Gallery: attrib., 1803; 92959 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH378)
- City Hall "Elevation of One half the Gallery Stretched out": pencil, MC, 1803; 92958 (Box Drawer 23, Item ch063)
- City Hall "West Front": pencil, LC, 1804; 92957 (Box Drawer 16, Item CH009)
- City Hall Elevation: attrib., 1803; 92956 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH388 verso)
- City Hall Fence with gate and piers: attrib., 1803; 92955 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH376)
- City Hall Window design: attrib., 1803; 92954 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH352)
- City Hall "Elevation of West Front": ink, LC, 1803; 92953 (Box Drawer 16, Item CH008)
- City Hall A Cornice, Second Order: attrib., 1803; 92952 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH086)
- City Hall "design for a Lewis at half Size": ink, UL-UC, 1803; 92951 (Box Drawer 11, Item CH033)
- City Hall Showing timbering Second Order: attrib., 1803; 92950 (Box Drawer 24, Item CH087)
- City Hall Statuary: attrib., 1803; 92949 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH354)
- City Hall "North Front": pencil, LR, 1803; 92948 (Box Drawer 20, Item CH049 1/2)
- City Hall "Supreme Court Room": pencil, LL-LC, 1803; 92947 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH385)
- City Hall Exterior? Details: attrib., 1803; 92946 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH325)
- City Hall Court Room: attrib., 1803; 92945 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH107)
- City Hall "Ionic Impost full Sise": ink, ML-MC, 1803; 92944 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH104)
- City Hall Volute and acanthus leaf details: attrib., 1803; 92943 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH047 verso)
- City Hall 3 Lamppost designs: attrib., 1803; 92942 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH374)
- City Hall "Myrtle Branch": ink, LL-LR, 1803; 92941 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH402)
- City Hall "Lorel Branch": ink, LL-LR, 1803; 92940 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH403)
- City Hall Reflected Ceiling Plan: attrib., 1803; 92939 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH078)
- City Hall "Olive Branch": ink, LL-LR, 1803; 92938 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH400)
- City Hall Doorway details: attrib., 1803; 92937 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH368)
- City Hall Doorway details: attrib., 1803; 92936 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH383 1/2)
- City Hall Court Room Schemes: attrib., 1803; 92935 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH104 verso)
- City Hall Urns: attrib., 1803; 92934 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH332)
- City Hall Sketches: attrib., 1803; 92933 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH107 verso)
- City Hall Interior Elevation: attrib., 1803; 92932 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH404)
- City Hall Gallery plan: attrib., 1803; 92931 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH378 verso)
- City Hall Doorway details: attrib., 1804; 92930 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH384 verso)
- City Hall Partial Elevation of Attic and Base of Cupola: attrib., 92929 (Box McComb Drawer 13, Item CH498)
- City Hall Landscape of Island and Lighthouse, [1803]; 92928 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH055 verso)
- City Hall Court Room: attrib., 1803; 92927 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH076)
- City Hall "Mouldings for Architrave & Pilaster of door in Supreme Court.": ink, MR-LR, 1803; 92926 (Box Drawer 13, Item CH072 1/2)
- City Hall "Impost for 2d Order": ink, UL, 1803; 92925 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH044)
- City Hall Entablature details: attrib., 1803; 92924 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH106 verso)
- City Hall Map of City Hall Park: attrib., 1803; 92923 (Box Drawer 24, Item CH088)
- City Hall "Mouldings for Center of Ceiling Common Council Chamber": ink, LR, 1803; 92922 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH328)
- City Hall Fence with gate and piers: attrib., 1803; 92921 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH375)
- City Hall "Equal to the projection in the rear of City Hall": pencil, ML-MR, 1803; 92920 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH371)
- City Hall Lamppost design: attrib., 1803; 92919 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH372)
- City Hall Grand Stair Scheme: attrib., 1803; 92918 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH329)
- City Hall Grand Stair Details: attrib., 1803; 92917 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH329 verso)
- City Hall Well executed detail of stairway, 1804; 92916 (Box Drawer 24, Item CH069)
- City Hall Gate and fence: attrib., 1803; 92915 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH373)
- City Hall "Middle door of Chancery Court": pencil, ML-MC, 1804; 92914 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH384)
- City Hall Sketch of Dome: attrib., 1803; 92913 (Box Drawer 21, Item CH053)
- City Hall Sketches - Capitals 2nd Order: attrib., 1804; 92912 (Box Drawer 18, Item CH037)
- City Hall Sketch of Cupola with Columns: attrib., 1803; 92911 (Box Drawer 21, Item CH052)
- City Hall Details: attrib., 1803; 92910 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH390 verso)
- City Hall "Section from East to West of Basement Story through CD": ink, MC, 1803; 92909 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH390)
- City Hall "BASEMENT STORY": ink, LC, 1803; 92908 (Box Drawer 8, Item CH011)
- City Hall Details: attrib., 1803; 92907 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH385 verso)
- City Hall "Capital for the 2"d Order of Pilasters for New City Hall": ink, LC, 1803; 92906 (Box Drawer 19, Item CH040)
- City Hall Base Plan of Cupola: attrib., 1803; 92905 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH089 verso)
- City Hall "Design for the Piers at the lower end of the Park": ink, LR, 1803; 92904 (Box Drawer 25, Item CH090)
- City Hall "Railing in Common Council Chamber": ink, MC-MR, 1803; 92903 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH091)
- City Hall 2 doorway designs: attrib., 1803; 92902 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH383)
- City Hall "Ivy Branch": ink, LL-LR, 1803; 92901 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH401)
- City Hall "Porters Lodge Lobby": pencil, LL, 1803; 92900 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH370)
- City Hall "Survey of Dr Osborns 2 Story T. Ho": pencil, UL-UR, 1803; 92899 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH368 verso)
- City Hall Plan of Second Floor: attrib., 1803; 92898 (Box Drawer 8, Item CH016)
- City Hall Entryway designs: attrib., 1803; 92897 (Box Drawer 14, Item CH097)
- City Hall Balustrade, [1803]; 92896 (Box Drawer 22, Item CH053 1/2)
- City Hall Doorways (2) and details: attrib., 1803; 92895 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH381)
- City Hall "Capital for 3/4 Columns- 2"d Order": ink, ML, [1803]; 92894 (Box Drawer 12, Item CH042)
- City Hall Vestibule and Portico: attrib., 1803; 92893 (Box Drawer 23, Item CH060)
- City Hall Park Railings, 1803; 92892 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH092)
- City Hall "Working Drawings of Fence as executed at City Hall Park about the year-": pencil, LL-LC, 1803; 92891 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH108)
- City Hall Working Drawing of Cupola - as executed., 1803; 92890 (Box Drawer 7, Item CH057)
- City Hall Park Plan ink, ML: "Plan shewing the situation of the Public Buildings near the East Wing of the New York Institution", 92889 (Box McComb Box 14, Item 233)
- City Hall Records McComb Letter regarding marble for City Hall: attrib., 1803; October 11; 92888 (Box McComb Box 22)
- City Hall Records John McComb Account Ledger for City Hall: attrib., 1812; 92887 (Box McComb Box 22)
- City Hall Records McComb Letter regarding a gold piece: attrib., 1824; post; 92886 (Box McComb Box 22)
- City Hall Records "3.d Bill Copy of a Bill for Marble for the New City Hall sent to Johnson &. Stevens at West Stockbridge on 23d July 1804 Am.t of Bill 3171'-, 1804; July 23; 92885 (Box McComb Box 22)
- City Hall Records "CHRONOLOGY OF EVENTS IN THE BUILDING OF THE CITY HALL": UL-UR, 1801-1956; 92884 (Box McComb Box 22)
- City Hall: attrib. Rear Elevation: attrib., [1804]; 92883 (Box McComb Drawer 13, Item CH389)
- City Hotel ink, LC: "Broad-Way - 100"4-", [1792]; 92882 (Box McComb Box 19, Item 396)
- City Hotel ink, LC: "Second Floor", [1792]; 92881 (Box McComb Box 19, Item 397)
- Coach house/ stable [attrib], 92880 (Box McComb box 1, Item 010b)
- Coles, John B. Esquire Residence ink, MC-ML: "Second and third Floors of a House disign'd for John B. Coles Esqr", 92879 (Box McComb box 6, Item 101)
- Coles, John B. Esquire Residence ink, UC-LC: "Basement & First Story of a House disign'd for John B. Coles Esquire", 92878 (Box McComb box 6, Item 100)
- Coles, John B. Esquire Residence ink, LL-LC: "Elevation of a House disign'd for John B. Coles Esquire on White Hall Street", 92877 (Box McComb box 6, Item 102a recto)
- Column volute, attrib., 92876 (Box McComb Box 20, Item 427 verso)
- Columns, paired and pier design Paired columns; rusticated pier: attributed, 92875 (Box McComb Box 17, Item 348)
- Construction details, attributed ink, UL-UR: "a Trussed Girder with the Truss mortised in with an Iron bolt and Screw Iron Plates at the ends of the Trusses", 92874 (Box McComb Box 20, Item 417)
- Construction details, attributed, 92873 (Box McComb Box 20, Item 418)
- Cornice moldings, attrib. pencil, UL-UR: "St Pauls NYC gallery front", 92872 (Box McComb Box 21, Item 456 bis)
- Cornices ink, ML: "Cornice at Large", 92871 (Box McComb Box 17, Item 338)
- Cornices, attached columns Designs for mantelpieces. Cf. Adam designs: attributed, 92870 (Box McComb Box 17, Item 334)
- Cornices, Doorways - 3 Detail of a column from a fireplace of Adam designs.: attributed, 92869 (Box McComb Box 17, Item 335)
- Country house, unidentified Front Elevation: attributed, 92868 (Box McComb Box 19, Item 407)
- Croton Aqueduct "Abstract of Corporation Ordinances and Rules adopted by the Croton Aqueduct Department,...", January 15, 1851; 92867 (Box McComb Box 17, Item 339 (2))
- Design for a Gazebo. [attrib in pencil on secondary support LC, by S. D. Stillman, 1955], 92866 (Box McComb box 1, Item 15)
- Design for ceiling, eagle and garlands, attrib., 92865 (Box McComb Box 16, Item 311)
- Detail Study of a furnace for heating, attrib., 92864 (Box McComb Box 21, Item 432)
- Distillery ink, ML-MC: "Plan of a distiliry for Martin Madan Esq", 92863 (Box McComb Box 13, Item 225)